[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "But we think, though, that maybe Michele Knight, who is the oldest of the three women, that she is the one that's been having most difficulties, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "RBS", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Well, that's what we've heard.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Knight"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "We're hearing that they may all be charged with kidnap and rape of these women, but have you heard any more?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, that would be a start, certainly, and as you mentioned, 36 hours, they must charge them within 36 hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Are you as amazed as the rest of us that they have been found right in the heart of the area where they were taken?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, yes, I am amazed at that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Are we still waiting for confirmation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "It's very -- I have a lot of mixed emotions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Faliceonna, you are I believe 16 years old, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "But at the time, did you take any action?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "No, I didn't, but I was kind of hurt that they didn't tell me as soon as they saw it, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Nina"]}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "I was dumbfounded, didn't know how to take it, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "And let me turn to you, Nina.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "What was he like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "He was -- he was fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Did you ever see them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Did you ever see -- sorry, yes, Annita?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", ":", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Annita"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Did you ever get into the house or the garden?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "We -- the closest I ever came to his house was to the door, and he had it cracked open and he gave us popsicles.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "How do you feel, Nina, finally, about the revelation that he may be this absolute monster along with his brothers, and there were three young women not entirely dissimilar ages to you when they were taken, who have been kept in this dungeon, no other way to describe it, for so long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nina"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Just to clarify for viewers, you have the same name as Gina DeJesus but you're not related at all, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "That I know of, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gina DeJesus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "That he may have been leading some strange other life you weren't privy to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Did she give any indication of how Gina is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "She did, a very positive report.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gina"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "INA SUMMERS, ASHLEY'S AUNT: Oh, I feel like I hope she does come back, and I hope that they do find her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Do you feel that in some way, her disappearance is connected to the disappearance of these other three young women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "It seems like it would, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Have you ever given up hope as a family that she would be alive out there somewhere?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "I have never gave up hope.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "What kind of person was your sister?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "She was outgoing, had a lot of friends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Do you feel, Debbie, that in your gut, that this is all connected, that the timing of when Ashley was taken, the age that she was, the area that she was taken, do you just feel collectively as a family this has to be connected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Yes, I do feel it's connected.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Debbie", "Ashley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Had you as a family been able to work out if there could have been any other reason why she would disappear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "And have you had any leads at all in the last few years as to what may have happened to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "We had a couple false ones.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last few years"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Have you been contacted at all by the police since the discovery of these three other women yesterday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "So that would be Ashley's mother they rang, was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Um-hum.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "And did the police give any suggestion that they believe that there may be a link here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Hello?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Are they on their way right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "As soon as we get a car open.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Who's the guy you're -- who's the guy who went out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "His name is Ariel Castro.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "How old is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "He's like 52.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Did you read anything else into her voice, into her demeanor in that call?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Well, no, I think she was very frightened and I think she had a very small time window that she was working at.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Would there have been some psychological hold that the owner of the house or the three brothers collectively had on them, either physically or mentally, that would have prevented them from doing that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Well, I think that's obvious that that's what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "She would require, I would imagine, pretty different treatment to the others because of her age?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Well, very different, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jaycee Dugard"]}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Is there anything, from everything you've seen, which should raise serious concern about the way the police have handled or mishandled this investigation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Well, listen, in the Jaycee Dugard case, we know there was an exhaustive review of law enforcement, and rightly so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Mark Geragos, would you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Geragos"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "They try to keep it in the locality if they can?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Well, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "But would you expect that to be the natural course of things tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Lisa Bloom, if it goes to trial, are these young women compelled to give evidence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "You know, I love that question, because I represent a lot of victims of sexual abuse.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lisa Bloom"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "The little girl is your baby?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Yes, she's my daughter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]